So now let's talk about Amazon bedrock agents.
So the agent is going to be a very smart thing
that is going to act a little bit like a human.
The idea is that instead of just asking questions
to a model, now the model is going to be able to start
thinking a little bit and to perform various multi-step tasks.
And these tasks may have an impact on our own databases
or our own infrastructure.
So the agent can actually create infrastructure.
It can deploy applications and can do operations
on our systems.
So here now the agent doesn't provide us information.
It also starts to think and act.
So for example, it's going to look at tasks
and then it's going to perform the task in the correct order
and ensure that the correct information
is passed within the task even if we haven't programmed
the agent to do so.
So what we do is that we are going to create
what's called action groups.
And the agent are going to be configured
to understand what these action groups do and what they mean.
And then automatically, the agent
will be able to integrate with other systems, services databases
and API to exchange data or to initiate action.
And also, if it needs to get some information
out of your systems in terms of unlabeled data,
it can look at RAG to retrieve the information
when necessary.
So that sounds a little bit magical,
but I will show you exactly how that works.
So in Amazon Bedrock, you would go and create an agent
and you are defining what the agent is responsible for.
So for example, you are an agent responsible
for accessing purchase history for our customers
as well as recommendations into what they can purchase next.
And you are responsible for placing new orders.
So the agent knows that it can do all these things.
So if the user is asking something for the agent
or the model to do one of these things,
Bedrock is smart is going to say,
well, this agent probably is going to be responsible
for these actions.
Then the agent knows about a few action groups.
So for example, we have defined an API,
it's a way to interface with our system.
And we have, for example, defined get recent purchases
or get recommended purchases or get purchase details
and then a specific purchase ID.
So all these things are known to the agent
in terms of what is the expected input for these APIs
and what do these APIs do?
What is the documentation around it?
And all this is provided thanks to an open API schema.
And so when done, well, the agent can invoke these
and behind the scenes, of course, interact
with our backend systems.
For example, make changes to our database.
The other way to set up an action group
is to use Lambda functions.
So Lambda functions are a way to run a little bit of code
in AWS without provisioning infrastructure.
So the Lambda functions again can be used to be created
and place an order through Lambda function.
And so it could use the same database or a new database.
But the idea is that I wanted to show here
that the agent can interact either with an external API
or with Lambda functions on your AWS accounts.
And finally, it has access to knowledge bases
that we define, of course.
And so for example, say we have a knowledge base
around our company, a shipping policy
and return policy, et cetera, et cetera.
So we could have those.
And so if the user is asking something about the return policy
for an order it's about to do,
the agent is smart enough to also provide that to the user.
So the agents are very smart and they know what to access
and then automatically we'll know how to do it.
So how does that work behind the scenes?
Well, say we have a task.
And we give this task to a bedrock agent.
Now the agent is going to look at the prompt.
He looks into look at all the conversation history,
look at all the actions available,
as well as the knowledge bases.
What are these structures and what is the task?
I'm just going to take all this information together
and send it to a generative AI model
backed by Amazon bedrock.
And say, please tell me how you would proceed
to perform these actions given all this information.
So it's using the chain of thoughts.
So in the fact means that the output of the bedrock model
is going to be a list of steps.
So step one into this.
Step two, do this.
Step three, do this and step n, last step, do that.
And so the steps are going to be executed by the agents.
And so first one, call an API call on this action group
and get the results.
Step two, do it against step three, call another API,
et cetera, et cetera.
Maybe you could use search into a knowledge base
and they get the results and so on.
But so the agent is going to work
and do all these things for us, thanks to the steps
that were generated by the bedrock model, which is amazing.
And then the final result is returned to the bedrock agent.
The bedrock agent then sends the tasks and the results
to another bedrock model.
And the bedrock model is going to synthesize everything
and give a final response to our user
and we'll get the final response.
So this is all happening behind the scenes.
Of course us, we'll just use the agent and the agent
that stuff and automatically we see the final response.
The bedrock is really nice because you actually
something called tracing on your agent
and this allows you to see the list of steps
that were done by the agent.
So you can debug in case you don't like a way
an agent performed something.
So that's it for Amazon bedrock agents.
I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture.